<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.5.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-08-08T21:49:42+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">DevOps diary</title><subtitle>Simple blog diary about my learning progress of AWS, Salt, Chef, Ansible and Jenkins.  Maybe little bit of security and cooking recepies.
</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello World!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/general/2017/08/08/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World!" /><published>2017-08-08T21:15:32+02:00</published><updated>2017-08-08T21:15:32+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/general/2017/08/08/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/general/2017/08/08/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;Hello everybody, my name is Norbert and I am working as a DevOps / System Integrator. 
On my daily basis I am working with Kubernetes, Docker, Salt and Jenkins - this is my main stack. However I feel that there is much to improve so I want to learn more about Salt and &lt;em&gt;Jenkins&lt;/em&gt;. AWS, Kubernetes and Google Cloud Platform are my second choice. I think that better understanding of these technologies allows me to improve my work and performance. So let’s start togherer! I will describe here all stuff I am learning and what is my progress in it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Hello everybody, my name is Norbert and I am working as a DevOps / System Integrator. On my daily basis I am working with Kubernetes, Docker, Salt and Jenkins - this is my main stack. However I feel that there is much to improve so I want to learn more about Salt and Jenkins. AWS, Kubernetes and Google Cloud Platform are my second choice. I think that better understanding of these technologies allows me to improve my work and performance. So let’s start togherer! I will describe here all stuff I am learning and what is my progress in it.</summary></entry></feed>